这是《权力的游戏》里的那把
It's from Game of Thrones.
你觉得怎样
What do you think?
不知道
I don't know.
如果我们要开始收藏奇幻剧中的刀剑
If we're going to start a fantasy sword collection--
虽然我很久前就认为应该收藏
and I've long thought we should--
但真的要从这把开始吗
is this really the sword to start with?
那你想从哪把开始
What did you have in mind?
我会不假思索地说  亚瑟王的神剑
Well, off the top of my head, I'd have to go with Excalibur.
它能赋予你统治英格兰的权力
It gives you the right to rule England.
那肯定是电影道具的复制品
It would be a replica of a movie prop.
也有道理
Fair enough.
那就是赋予你统治英格兰复制品的权力
It'd give you the right to rule a replica of England.
这里没有亚瑟王的神剑
Well, they don't have an Excalibur here,
你觉得该怎么办
so what do you want to do?
真是艰难的抉择
Mm. Tough decision.
这里没有中国血汗工厂伪造的那种
There's no weaponry from Lord of the Rings
《指环王》里的武器吗
forged in a Chinese sweatshop?
只有比尔博·巴金斯的剑在那边
Just Bilbo Baggins' sword over there.
俩成年男子拿着把霍比特人的短剑  看着不傻吗
Two grown men with a hobbit's dagger; wouldn't we look silly?
好了  就这把了
Okay, let's go for it.
两位发现了我的小宝贝
Oh, I see you guys have found my little treasure.
是啊
Yeah.
看着还行
It's okay, I guess.
什么叫还行  它简直了不起
Okay? It's magnificent.
多少钱
What do you want for it?
很难给本尊出现在付费电视上
Oh, it's hard to put a price on something
其复制品出现在本店里的东西定价
that's a copy of something that was on pay cable.
不过卖给朋友嘛  就二百五吧
But for my friends, let's say 250?
你还真是狮子大开口
Oh, that's pretty steep.
这可是限量版
Well, it's a limited edition.
只生产了八千把哦
They only made 8,000 of these bad boys.
只有八千把
Only 8,000?
我们在浪费宝贵时间  快买下
We're wasting precious time. Buy it.
等等
Hang on.
还能少点吗
Can you do any better?
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding?
这已经是亲友折扣了
I'm already giving you the friends and family discount.
听到了吗
Oh, did you hear that?
人家都给我们亲友折扣了
We're getting the friends and family discount.
我们很荣幸  这就买了
We are honored and we will take it.
慢着
Slow down.
二百块
Two hundred.
你在做什么啊
What are you doing?
二百五已经是折扣价了
250 is already the discounted price.
闭嘴吧你
Will you shut up?
这样吧  二百三十五好了
Tell you what, I'll go 235.
那算了  下次买吧
Nope. Maybe another time.
好吧  二百二十五  这是最终报价
Okay, 225-- my final offer.
买下吧  买下吧
Take it, take it.
二百块
Two hundred.
天  你是要杀了我
Man, you're killing me!
杀你?  我都喘不过气了
Killing you? I can't breathe.
二百一吧  亏本卖了
210, and I'm losing money.
不能欺人太甚  莱纳德  太对不起了
Oh, now, we can't let him lose money, Leonard. I'm so sorry.
二百一  再送个《钢铁侠》里的头盔
210 and you throw in the Iron Man helmet.
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?
那头盔上有小罗伯特·唐尼的签名
That helmet's signed by Robert Downey Jr.
那又怎样
So?
好吧  如果你要质疑
Okay, if you're going to question
一个来自漫画改编的电影  还有演员签名的
the importance of an actor's signature on a plastic helmet
塑料头盔的重要性
from a movie based on a comic book,
那我们这群人的生活  还有什么意义可言
then all of our lives have no meaning!
好吧
Okay, fine.
就这把剑  二百一
Just the sword, 210.
谢谢
Thank you.
这周有肉吃啦
I can eat meat this week.
看到没
See that?
我帮我们省了四十块
I just saved us 40 bucks.
我早就说过  你学术知识的匮乏
I've long said, what you lack in academic knowledge
全弥补在市井小民的小聪明上了
you make up for in street smarts.
要包起来吗
You want me to wrap it?
不用了
No, it's okay.
我要用它直刺我朋友胸口
I'm gonna stab my friend in the chest.
嗨  斯图尔特
Hey, Stuart.
嗨  威尔
Ah, hey, Wil.
哈罗  威尔·惠顿
Hello, Wil Wheaton.
嗨  谢尔顿
Hi, Sheldon.
好剑
Nice sword.
这是我刀剑收藏中的其中一把
It's part of my sword collection.
-你有收藏刀剑吗  -没有
- Do you have a sword collection?  - No.
我一点都不奇怪
I'm not surprised.
这是《蝙蝠侠》第612期
Here's the Batman 612
有你想要的吉姆·李重新画的封面
with the Jim Lee alternate cover that you wanted.
太棒了  多少
Awesome. What do I owe you?
四十块
40 bucks.
真划算
Good deal.
笨蛋
Sucker.
他都没要个亲友折扣
Didn't even ask for the friends and family discount.
周五我要在家办个派对
Hey, I'm having a party at my house on Friday,
希望你能来
and I was hoping you would stop by.
有女孩子吗
Will there be girls there?
当然有
Yeah, of course.
上次就没有
'Cause there wasn't last time.
这次肯定有
There will be girls.
你们想来的话  我也邀请你们哦
You guys are invited if you want to come by.
谢谢你
Thank you.
好了  非常好
All right, great.
回见
Later.
我知道你的小把戏
I see what you're doing.
你接受了
You accept an invitation
去我死敌家参加派对的邀请
to a party at the home of my sworn enemy,
他就会大肆宣扬  我们俩会去
he tells everyone we're going to be there,
而我们不去  他就成了傻瓜
and when we don't show, he looks the fool.
很坏很聪明
Fiendishly clever.
我是真的想去
I was actually thinking about going.
去了说一句  这派对烂死了  然后摔门而去
And then declaring the party a fiasco and storming out,
让他在客人面前颜面尽失
leaving him humiliated in front of his guests.
我喜欢
Love it.
不是  我要带上拉杰和霍华德
No, I was gonna grab Raj and Howard
我们要好好玩
and have a good time.
太好了  僧多粥少
Oh, great, more guys.
威尔·惠顿又筹办了一个光"棍"派对
It's gonna be another Wil Wheaton sausage-fest.
谢尔顿  能给拿瓶水吗
Sheldon, can you grab me a water?
可能可以
Possibly.
到底可不可以
Can you or can't you?
这事没那么简单  莱纳德
It's not that simple, Leonard.
什么到你那  都复杂了
It never is, is it?
目前  咱俩的关系
At this moment,our relationship exists
处于两种相互矛盾的状态
in two mutually contradictory states.
在你决定去  或是不去
Until you either do not go or go
威尔·惠顿的派对之前
to Wil Wheaton's party,
你是我的朋友  同时又不是我的朋友
you are simultaneously my friend and not my friend.
我把这个现象称为
I'm characterizing this phenomenon
薛定谔的友谊
as Schrodinger's Friendship.
明白了  可以把水给我了吗
Got it. Can I have my water?
当然
Of course.
自己捡去吧  你这个叛徒
Now get it yourself, you traitor.
等一下  这到底是怎么回事
Wait, what is going on?
忘了我就再提醒你一下
In case you have forgotten,
薛定谔的猫是个理想实验
Schrodinger's cat is a thought experiment...
不  不  我没忘
No, no, I didn't forget.
他把一只猫装进了盒子  在你打开盒子之前
Um, there's this cat in a box and until you open it,
猫要么死  要么活  要么半死半活
it's either dead or alive or both.
尽管在我内布拉斯卡州的老家
Although, back in Nebraska,
我们家的猫钻进了我哥露营用的行李箱里
our cat got stuck in my brother's camp trunk,
我们不用打开就知道
and we did not need to open it
里面肯定装满了各式各样的死猫
to know there was all kinds of dead cat in there.
会讲家常小故事  懂点物理
Homespun stories, knowledge of physics
同时还具有傲人的双峰
and a bosom that defies it.
你还真是全才啊
You're the whole package, aren't you?
抱歉  我来晚了
Sorry I'm late.
我有好消息要宣布
Uh, I got great news.
NASA[国家航空航天局]选中了我们小组
NASA picked my team's design
设计的深空太空望远镜
for the deep field space telescope
今春天就要把这个设计用在国际空间站上了
that's going on the International Space Station this spring.
华仔  这太棒了
Howie, that's wonderful!
恭喜你
Congratulations!
精彩的还在后头呢
It gets better.
安装的时候还要派一个人
Someone has to go up with the telescope
作为装备专家上太空
as a payload specialist,
猜猜他们选中谁了
and guess who that someone is.
穆罕默德·李
Muhammad Li.
穆罕默德·李是谁
Who's Muhammad Li?
穆罕默德是全球最普遍的名
Muhammad is the most common first name in the world,
而李则是最普遍的姓氏
Li, the most common surname.
因为我不知道答案
As I didn't know the answer,
但我觉得这么猜  在数学上比较靠谱
I thought that gave me a mathematical edge.
他们选中我  谢尔顿
It's me, Sheldon.
是我
It's me.
我要上太空了
I'm going up in space!
严格来说  我是宇航员了
Technically, I'm an astronaut.
帅呆了
That's amazing!
等会儿
Hang on a second.
NASA已经没有航天飞机了
NASA doesn't have a shuttle anymore.
你怎么上太空呀
How are you going to get up there?
这个过程就酷了
Oh, well, it's really cool.
你先飞到莫斯科  然后他们带你去哈萨克斯坦
You fly to Moscow, they take you out to Kazakhstan,
然后你再登上一个俄罗斯联盟号火箭
and then you get into a Russian Soyuz rocket
直接冲上低空地球轨道
which shoots you into a low earth orbit.
又或是你只能呆坐在火箭发射台上
Or just sits there on the launch pad
因为哈萨克黑手党
because the Kazakhi mafia
把火箭燃料都拿到黑市上去卖了
sold the rocket fuel on the black market.
这些俄罗斯火箭安全吗
Are those Russian rockets safe?
切尔诺贝利事件也是这帮俄罗斯人弄出来的
Well, I mean, safe as it can be when it was built
安全性可见一斑吧
by the good folks who brought you Chernobyl.
我们大家来敬他一杯吧
I'd like to propose a toast.
我们在座的各位  都有登上太空的梦想
The dream to go up into space is one we all share,
而今天霍华德  实现了这个梦想
and Howard's making that a reality.
我们都以你为傲
We're all very proud of you.
干杯
Cheers.
敬酒词说的不错呀
That was a lovely toast.
-口头表扬一次  -谢谢
- Kudos.  - Thank you.
与此同时  你的敬酒词也老套得让人反胃
Simultaneously, a festival of cloying cliche.
你恶心死我了
You sicken me.
你怎么这么安静
You're really quiet.
没事吧
Is everything okay?
没事
Fine.
只是有点累了
Just a little tired.
希望你别太累  因为我现在可是
I hope not too tired, because I'm feeling
"阳刚"十足哦
particularly masculine right now.
蓄势待发  你明白我意思吧
All systems go, if you catch my drift.
我一向明白你意思
I always catch your drift.
好吧  你很明显是有心事
All right, well, something's obviously bugging you.
到底怎么了
What is it?
我只是不敢相信你居然
I just can't believe you signed up
都不跟我商量就决定上太空了
for the space program without even talking to me.
我明白了
Oh, I get it.
你是在担心我
You're worried about me.
你真是贴心啊  宝贝儿
That is so sweet.
在我们NASA有一句老话
You know, there's a saying we have at NASA.
太空英雄之所以成为英雄
What makes the right stuff so right
是因为他们能平安归来
is that it always comes home.
你就闭嘴吧  霍华德
Just stop talking, Howard.
我跟你说我要成为宇航员时
This isn't the reaction I expected
我可没想到你会是这么个反应
when I told you I was gonna be an astronaut.
那你以为我会是什么反应
What did you think was going to happen?
实话吗  当然是滚床单
Honestly? Sex.
霍华德
Howard.
你知道这是多大的事吗
Do you realize what a big deal this is?
你知道被选中上太空是何等的荣誉吗
What an honor it is to be chosen to go into space?
我明白
Yeah, I get it.
我只是希望你做决定之前能跟我商量一下
I just wish you included me in the decision.
咱俩应该是人生搭档
We're supposed to be partners.
应该是站在同一战线的
We're supposed to be a team.
对不起  你说的没错
I'm sorry. You're right.
好吧  咱重头来一次
Okay, let's try this again.
伯纳黛特  我现在遇到一个千载难逢的机遇
Bernadette, an opportunity has come up
事关咱俩  所以我想跟你商量一下
that impacts both of us, and I'd like to discuss it.
好吧
Okay.
我被NASA选中
I've been offered a chance to go up
要去国际空间站待上三个星期
to the International Space Station for three weeks.
你怎么想
What are your thoughts on that?
首先  我想谢谢你
Well, first of all, thank you
在做决定之前想到要跟我商量
for including me in the decision-making process.
那是当然  咱俩可是一个阵营的
Hey, we're a team.
那说说你的想法吧
So, what do you think?
不行
No.
No?
不行
No.
为什么不行
Why not?
霍华德  我父亲是个警察
Howard, my father was a police officer.
我们家人每天都提心吊胆的
We never knew from one night to the next
不知道他晚上能不能活着回到家
if he was going to come home alive.
那感觉糟透了
It was horrible.
我不希望跟你以后的生活也是这个样子
And I don't want to live that way with you.
我十一岁的时候
Hey, my father abandoned me and my mother
我爸就抛弃了我和我妈
when I was 11.
我们从那以后再没见过他
We never saw him again.
说啥都没用  反正我就是不许你上太空
Oh, boo-hoo, you're not going to space!
霍华德还挺有能耐的  对吧
Pretty cool about Howard, huh?
别装作咱俩之间好像没事一样
Don't talk to me as if nothing's happened between us.
不过没错  他是挺有能耐的  兄弟
And yes, it sure is, buddy.
老天啊  你能不能别再玩薛定谔那一套了
For God's sake, will you stop with the Schrodinger stuff.
你想要像海森堡不确定性原理
Would you prefer a simpler application
那样更简单的程序吗
of Heisenberg's uncertainty principle,
我现在不能同时确定
in which I could either
你到底是哪方的或我是否喜欢你
know where you are or whether I like you,
不过现在两者都不确定
but not both.
你是从不知道住嘴的  是吧
You never stop talking, do you?
我不明白
I don't understand.
莱纳德去不去威尔·惠顿的派对
What differences does it make
有什么区别
if Leonard goes to Wil Wheaton's party?
威尔·惠顿是谢尔顿的死敌
Wil Wheaton is Sheldon's mortal enemy.
死敌
Mortal enemy?
谢尔顿  我知道你是个
Sheldon, I know you're a bit
十分别扭的人  但是
of a left-handed monkey wrench, but...
你真的有个死敌吗
you really have a mortal enemy?
其实我有61个
In fact, I have 61 of them.
你想看看我的黑名单吗
Would you like to see the list?
说不要  说不要  说不要
Oh, say no, say no, say no, say no.
刚刚才把你从名单上剔除
You just got off the list.
是不是又想回去了
Would you like back on it?
这要稍等一下
This'll just take a moment.
名单存在一张5.25英寸软盘里
It's on a five and a quarter inch floppy.
你还用软盘啊
A floppy disk?
我九岁就开始列这个名单了
Well, I started the list when I was nine.
威尔·惠顿为啥被列入名单了
How did Wil Wheaton get on the list?
-老天  -别问啊
- Oh, God! - Oh! Come on!
我小的时候非常喜欢卫斯理·柯洛夏
As a child, I loved Wesley Crusher,
即威尔·惠顿在《星际迷航》里的角色
Wil Wheaton's character on Star Trek.
我坐了几小时巴士  去参加一个星际迷航大会
So, I drove for hours by bus to a Star Trek convention
威尔·惠顿本来是要出席的
at which Wil Wheaton was scheduled to appear,
我要找他给我的卫斯理·柯洛夏玩具签名
so that I could get my Wesley Crusher action figure signed.
可他压根就没出现
But he never showed, because
因为他去玩"好莱坞框框"了
apparently, it was cooler for him
他觉得坐左下角那框框里更酷
to be the lower-left corner on Hollywood Squares.
该死
Oh, damn!
软盘挂了
The floppy failed.
好吧  不管是谁在1989年
Well, whoever was in charge of quality control
负责威宝公司的质量控制
at the Verbatim Corporation in 1989,
恭喜他  他进了我的黑名单
congratulations, you just made the list.
霍华德
Howard?
改变主意要滚床单了吗
Change your mind about sex?
虽然还生气  但我会委曲求全
I'm still mad, but I'll do it.
不是  我刚刚一直在想
No, I've just been thinking.
我担心你的安危并不重要
It doesn't matter if I'm afraid for your safety.
重要的是  我不想成为那个
I don't want to be the person
阻碍你追逐梦想的人
who stands between you and your dreams.
真的吗
Really?
真的
Really.
如果去太空真的对你很重要
If going into space means that much to you,
我不会再说一句反对的话
I will never say another word about it.
谢谢
Thank you.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
那现在开滚[床单]了吗
So, sex now?
好
Okay.
不过我刚忘了刷牙
I just forgot to brush my teeth.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
*哦  宝贝 *
* Oh, baby
*我...*
* I'm
*我爱的不是你 *
* I'm not in love with you...
除非我死  否则我儿子休想去太空
Over my dead body my son goes into outer space!
我准备好了
I'm ready.
等等  先看看我理解得对不对
Wait, let me see if I got this right.
你真的半夜
You actually asked Bernadette
把伯纳黛特赶出了家门?
to leave your house in the middle of the night?
我有得选吗
What choice did I have?
她背着我
She went behind my back
告发我妈来反我
and turned my own mother against me.
哇  你不仅是我们中的第一个宇航员
Wow. You're not only our first astronaut.
还是我们中第一个把女孩子赶下床的人
You're also the first one of us to kick a girl out of bed.
你简直就是个巨星啊
You're like a rock star.
有点吧
Little bit.
我不想这么说  但她确实背叛了你
I hate to say it, but she did kind of betray you.
真有意思
Interesting.
你能看出别人的背叛行为  却看不出你自己的
You see betrayal in others, but not yourself.
去惠顿的派对不是背叛你
Going to Wheaton's party is not betraying you.
你当然会这么认为
Oh, of course you would have to believe that.
邪恶的人永远认为自己是对的
Evil always thinks it's doing right.
"喂  突击兵"
"Excuse me, Stormtrooper. "
"这些才是你要找的机器人"
"These are the droids you're looking for."
我是去参加派对
I'm going to a party.
又不是叫R2-D2和C-3PO机器人反帝国
I'm not turning R2-D2 and C-3PO over to the empire!
时候未到而已
Not yet.
那接下来怎样
So, what's gonna happen next?
你和伯纳黛特会分手吗
Are you and Bernadette going to break up?
我不知道
I don't know.
就算我们要复合
If we're going to get back together,
她也要先道歉  并且接受
she's going to have to apologize and accept  that
我是个大男人  我能自己拿主意
I'm a grown man who can make his own decisions.
然后她还要说服你妈  让你去太空
Then she's going to have to convince your mother to let you go into space.
必须的
Obviously.
我没有别的办法
I had no choice.
我必须告诉他妈
I had to tell his mother.
他不能去太空
He can't go to space.
他还是只小雏鸟呢
He's like a baby bird.
你知道他有一次
Do you know he once got an asthma attack
因为看图书馆的旧书引发哮喘吗
from reading an old library book?
开玩笑的吧
You're kidding.
真的  我那天还在场呢
No, I was there that day.
谢尔顿递那本书给他时  还闪到腰了
Sheldon threw his back out handing him that book.
我不知道自己该怎么办
I don't know what I'm going to do.
我不想因此和他分手
I don't want to break up over this.
好吧  那你直接跟他说你错了
Okay, why don't you just tell him you made a mistake?
你们觉得我做错了吗
Do you guys think it was a mistake?
我这样是不是太小人了
Am I the bad guy in this?
这事轮不到我们来评论
It's not for us to judge.
我们只是来支持你  安慰你
We're just here to provide comfort and support
你要自己面对你的小人之举
while you come to grips with what a despicable thing you've done.
天啊  你说得对
Oh, God, you're right.
我把我们的爱扔到了他那肥婆老妈脚下
I took our love and threw it under his bus-sized mother.
我得去道歉
I need to apologize.
那也对  我很高兴你想通了
Well, that-that's good. I'm glad you came to that.
不过在此之前  我想问你一个重点问题
But before you do, let me just ask you a big picture question.
什么问题
What?
你确定一定以及肯定
Are you 100% positive
你爱霍华德·沃罗威茨而且想嫁给他吗
you love and want to marry Howard Wolowitz?
当然  发自肺腑地想
I do, with all my heart.
明白了  就是确认一下
Got it.  Just had to check.
他是好男人哦
He's great.
谢尔顿
All right, Sheldon.
我们要去威尔家了
We're going to Wil's.
这是你最后的机会
This is your last chance.
不对  莱纳德  这是你最后的机会
No, Leonard, this is your last chance.
总有一天
One day,
会有一位历史学家来问你
a historian is going to come to you and say,
你真的曾是谢尔顿·库珀博士的朋友吗
"Is it true you were friends with Dr. Sheldon Cooper?"
然后你就会一边
And you're going to have to
饱含悔恨与耻辱地呜咽着
choke back a hot sob of regret and humiliation
一边说  没错  但是
as you mumble, "I was, but
我当初选择去了一个
I chose to go to a party
由不知名电影《伴我同行》里某人办的派对
thrown by the one kid from Stand By Me that no one remembers."
-你想开车吗  -好啊
- You want to drive? - Sure.
-喂  谢尔顿  -太好了
- Hey, Sheldon? - Oh, good.
你选了我  你最后还是选了我
You picked me, you picked me.
不  我就是刚收到斯图尔特的一条短信
No, I just got a text from Stuart.
布伦特·斯派尔也在派对上
Brent Spiner is at the party.
布伦特·斯派尔
Brent Spiner?
对
Yes.
我没兴趣
I don't care.
真的吗
Really?
布伦特·斯派尔
Brent Spiner,
数据先生的扮演者  你可喜欢他了
Mr. Data himself. You love him.
以前喜欢  但我现在已经对《星际迷航》不感冒了
I did, but I think I've kind of outgrown Star Trek.
你看啊  角色又老套
You know, stock characters,
情节又离谱  "传送我吧"
ludicrous plots, "Beam me up."
真是满嘴荒唐言啊
What a load of hooey.
我走了
I'm going.
生生不息  繁荣昌盛哦  谢尔顿
Live long and prosper, Sheldon.
嗯啊  随你怎么样  看着真傻
Yeah, even that. You look like a dork.
霍华德  伯纳黛特来了
Howard, Bernadette's here!
跟她说我不在家
Tell her I'm not home!
你怎么可以装得这么蹩脚
What kind of a schmuck play is that?!
她听得见你大声嚷嚷
She can hear you shouting!
能说句话吗
Can we talk?
你说啊  我没什么可说的
You can. I have nothing to say.
好吧
All right.
我就是想告诉你
I just wanted to tell you
我不该给你妈妈打小报告的  我很抱歉
I'm sorry I said something to your mother.
我本来是打算最后告诉她的
I was gonna tell her eventually,
可你居然背着我
but you went behind my back.
我知道  我错了
I know. I'm sorry.
我当时害怕啊
I got scared.
如果你要爱我
If you're gonna love me,
你就得爱我的全部
you're gonna have to love the whole package:
温柔诗人和疯狂泼皮都是我啊
the tenderhearted poet and the crazy daredevil.
我知道
I know.
如果你不是真心的就别这么说
Well, don't say it if you're not gonna mean it,
因为我不止要去空间站
'cause I'm not just gonna stop with the space station.
我还想去月球  想去火星
Yeah, I want to go to the Moon, I want to go to Mars.
想乘坐单人潜艇到大洋的最深处
I want to take a one-man sub to the lowest depths of the ocean.
真的吗
Really?
你在加勒比海盗船上都晕船了
You got seasick on Pirates of the Caribbean.
那几个胖小子非要摇来摇去
Well, those big kids were rocking it.
我之前那么做只是因为我太爱你了
I just did what I did because I love you so much,
我抑制不住害怕失去你的担心
and the thought of losing you is more than I can handle.
真的吗
Really?
你是我的灵魂伴侣
You're my soul mate.
你现在该吻我了
This is where you kiss me.
对对
Right, right.
你想干嘛都随你
Make up all you want!
但你休想离开地球半步
Your tuchis is not leaving this planet!
你知道那个在《星际迷航之第一次接触》里
Hey, you know that beautiful actress who plays
扮演博格女王的漂亮女演员吗
the Borg Queen in First Contact?
-知道啊  -我刚刚碰到她的妇科医生了
- Yeah. - Well, I just met her gynecologist!
你来这儿干嘛
What are you doing here?
为我们的友谊奋斗
Fighting for our friendship.
尽管你古怪又讨人嫌
As peculiar and annoying as you can be,
但你还是我的好哥们儿
you're still my little buddy.
今晚我不能让我们的友谊在这里毁掉
I'm not going to let that end here tonight.
赶紧把杯子放下  咱见完布伦特·斯派尔就走人
Now put down that drink, let's meet Brent Spiner and go home.
嗨  谢尔顿  很高兴你也来了
Hey, Sheldon, I'm so glad you made it.
有样东西我想你可能会喜欢
I found something I think you might like.
他要是有个更无趣的家我就更高兴了
What I'd like is for him to have a more depressing home.
可这地儿真不赖
This is quite lovely.
这是给你的
This is for you.
原版未拆封的卫斯理·柯洛夏活动人偶
An original mint-in-package Wesley Crusher action figure.
我记得你说过有一次
I remembered your story about the time you went
你小时候去动漫大会
to a convention when you were a kid
想拿到一个签名版的  但我没去
to get one signed, and I didn't show up.
看看我都写了啥
Look at what I wrote.
"谢尔顿  很抱歉东西来得这么迟
"To Sheldon, sorry this took so long.
你的朋友  威尔·威顿"
Your friend, Wil Wheaton."
这是我的最后一个
It's my last one.
我想把它送给你
I want you to have it.
看啊  各位  威尔·威顿现在是我朋友了
Look, everyone. Wil Wheaton is my friend!
我好多年没见过这东西了
I haven't seen one of these in years.
还记得我们以前怎么把他们摆的
Remember how we used to make these things look
看起来像在打手枪吗
like they were masturbating?
布伦特·斯派尔  你都干了些什么
Brent Spiner, what have you done?!
这可是原版未拆封全新的
That was an original mint-in-package
卫斯理·柯洛夏活动人偶
Wesley Crusher action figure
上面有我的铁哥们儿威尔·威顿签名的
signed by my close personal friend, Wil Wheaton.
抱歉了  竹竿男
Sorry, Slim.
我的车后备箱还有几个数据先生的玩偶
I've got some Mr. Data dolls in the trunk of my car.
你想要我也给你签一个吗
You want me to sign one for you?
您已经签了  布伦特·斯派尔
You've already signed something, Brent Spiner.
在我的黑名单上
Your name on my list.
从现在起  你就是我的死敌
From this moment on, you are my mortal enemy.
别担心  你当不了太久
Don't worry. It doesn't take up a whole lot of your time.
来吧  伙计
Come on, buddy.
别再这个懦夫这儿浪费时间了
Let's not waste another second on this loser.
好喜欢你家房子啊
Love your house.
能给我们签名玩偶吗
Can we get autographed dolls?
当然
Sure.
二十块
20 bucks.
十块
10.
十八块
18.
十二块
12.
十六块
16.
三十块拿俩
Two for $30.
外加来参加我的生日派对
And you come to my birthday party.
成交
Done.